<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Personal Development on EXIA&#39;s Garden</title>
    <link>https://exiasgarden.pages.dev/categories/personal-development/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Personal Development on EXIA&#39;s Garden</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2022 09:03:30 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://exiasgarden.pages.dev/categories/personal-development/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>If You Don&#39;t Have Regrets You&#39;re Doing Life Wrong</title>
      <link>https://exiasgarden.pages.dev/posts/if-you-dont-have-regrets-youre-doing-life-wrong/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2022 09:03:30 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://exiasgarden.pages.dev/posts/if-you-dont-have-regrets-youre-doing-life-wrong/</guid>
      <description>We all are taught, &amp;ldquo;Live a life, where you don&amp;rsquo;t have any regrets&amp;rdquo;, You subscribe to the idea and think &amp;ldquo;OK, I&amp;rsquo;ll live a life, where I don&amp;rsquo;t have any regrets!&amp;rdquo;, This sounds great from a macro perspective, but once you start to look at things from a microscopic level you start to see how difficult and punishing this kind of mindset can be.
Just to be clear, I&amp;rsquo;m not going to be talking about the obvious things one must do to avoid regrets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>✍🏻 Learn To Write</title>
      <link>https://exiasgarden.pages.dev/moc/level-64/learn-to-write/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Nov 2022 14:45:30 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://exiasgarden.pages.dev/moc/level-64/learn-to-write/</guid>
      <description>Jordan Peterson says that in order to think well its best to learn to write. When you can organize your thoughts well on a paper (or in this any digital format like this one) it helps you see things better in your head. And he is not the first one to say this I think.
I remember writing something similar when I was writing a post on insightfulsage.com. It said something similar, that organzing your thoughts on a paper helps you see them clearly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>🔎 Finding Meaning In Life With Friends And Family</title>
      <link>https://exiasgarden.pages.dev/posts/finding-meaning-with-friends-and-family/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 22:21:30 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://exiasgarden.pages.dev/posts/finding-meaning-with-friends-and-family/</guid>
      <description>Friends and family are the most important part of my life, like for many others. I cannot imagine my life without these people. Although it&amp;rsquo;s hard to explain what they mean to me or how friends and family can give your life meaning but, Here&amp;rsquo;s what I have. I might not be able to formulate all my thoughts properly, So I might add another post in the future.
They Love Me For Who I&amp;rsquo;m&gt; They Love Me For Who I&amp;rsquo;m # Friends and family love you for who you are.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>😇 How To Become A Good Friend</title>
      <link>https://exiasgarden.pages.dev/posts/how-to-be-a-good-friend/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2022 20:47:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://exiasgarden.pages.dev/posts/how-to-be-a-good-friend/</guid>
      <description>Who Is A Friend?&gt; Who Is A Friend? # It can be easy and hard to define what friendship is depending on who you&amp;rsquo;re talking to, but as I&amp;rsquo;m getting older the more I look into it, the better I feel about the friends that I have in my life.
So who is a friend? A friend can be anyone, even a family member, if they fulfil some of these roles -</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
