<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Fleeting Notes on EXIA&#39;s Garden</title>
    <link>exiagarden.github.io/categories/fleeting-notes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Fleeting Notes on EXIA&#39;s Garden</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 23:32:30 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="exiagarden.github.io/categories/fleeting-notes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Compassion In Humans And The Future</title>
      <link>exiagarden.github.io/posts/compassion-in-humans-and-the-future/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 23:32:30 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>exiagarden.github.io/posts/compassion-in-humans-and-the-future/</guid>
      <description>Do humans need to create a standard for compassion and empathy&gt; Do humans need to create a standard for compassion and empathy # We as humans are getting smarter with time but as all we do is get intelligence that doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean that are getting equally compassionate or moral. Going into the future with just intelligence is like shooting a gun but unable to see anything. It can lead to many disasters as people put their own self interests and wants before anything else.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Productivity Hacks</title>
      <link>exiagarden.github.io/posts/productivitty-hacks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Oct 2021 14:23:30 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>exiagarden.github.io/posts/productivitty-hacks/</guid>
      <description>1. Use A Calender&gt; 1. Use A Calender # Use calendar and time block to make sure you are doing what you&amp;rsquo;re supposed to be doing, this also helps with reminders.
2. Create A &amp;ldquo;Might-Do List&amp;rdquo; Of Daily Tasks&gt; 2. Create A &amp;ldquo;Might-Do List&amp;rdquo; Of Daily Tasks # These are the potential things I can do in the day.
Also add on &amp;ldquo;Highlight of the day&amp;rdquo; task. This is the most important task of the day, if this is done the day can be considered a success.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Compounded Relationships</title>
      <link>exiagarden.github.io/posts/compounded-relationships/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Aug 2021 13:41:30 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>exiagarden.github.io/posts/compounded-relationships/</guid>
      <description>Like compound interest in financial market and money we can also get compound interest/benefits in our relationships. Imagine investing in a good relationship for a long time, this relationship will give you more benefits than if you were to start that relationship and break it in between then start it again and do the same thing. With time relationships have the potential to grow at an exponential rate. It depends on how one manages the relationship.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
