<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>EXIA&#39;s Garden</title>
    <link>exiagarden.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on EXIA&#39;s Garden</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Nov 2022 14:45:30 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="exiagarden.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>✍🏻 Learn To Write</title>
      <link>exiagarden.github.io/posts/learn-to-write/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Nov 2022 14:45:30 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>exiagarden.github.io/posts/learn-to-write/</guid>
      <description>Jordan Peterson says that in order to think well its best to learn to write. When you can organize your thoughts well on a paper (or in this any digital format like this one) it helps you see things better in your head. And he is not the first one to say this I think.
I remember writing something similar when I was writing a post on insightfulsage.com. It said something similar, that organzing your thoughts on a paper helps you see them clearly.</description>
      <media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/exiagarden.github.io/posts/learn-to-write/feature.jpg" />
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>🔎 Finding Meaning In Life With Friends And Family</title>
      <link>exiagarden.github.io/posts/finding-meaning-with-friends-and-family/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 22:21:30 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>exiagarden.github.io/posts/finding-meaning-with-friends-and-family/</guid>
      <description>Friends and family are the most important part of my life, like for many others. I cannot imagine my life without these people. Although it&amp;rsquo;s hard to explain what they mean to me or how friends and family can give your life meaning but, Here&amp;rsquo;s what I have. I might not be able to formulate all my thoughts properly, So I might add another post in the future.
They Love Me For Who I&amp;rsquo;m&gt; They Love Me For Who I&amp;rsquo;m # Friends and family love you for who you are.</description>
      <media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/exiagarden.github.io/posts/finding-meaning-with-friends-and-family/feature.jpg" />
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>😇 How To Become A Good Friend</title>
      <link>exiagarden.github.io/posts/how-to-be-a-good-friend/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2022 20:47:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>exiagarden.github.io/posts/how-to-be-a-good-friend/</guid>
      <description>Who Is A Friend?&gt; Who Is A Friend? # It can be easy and hard to define what friendship is depending on who you&amp;rsquo;re talking to, but as I&amp;rsquo;m getting older the more I look into it, the better I feel about the friends that I have in my life.
So who is a friend? A friend can be anyone, even a family member, if they fulfil some of these roles -</description>
      <media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/exiagarden.github.io/posts/how-to-be-a-good-friend/feature.jpg" />
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>❤️‍🔥 The Beauty Inside</title>
      <link>exiagarden.github.io/posts/the-beauty-inside/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 04:15:30 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>exiagarden.github.io/posts/the-beauty-inside/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s a beauty inside all of us, although we may not see it all the time but, there are times when we see a glimpse of this beauty.
It can be a strangers smile, It can be a gesture, it can be anything that gives us a window to see into the souls of others.
Yesterday I saw a blind girl walking down the street, I don&amp;rsquo;t know what she was thinking but was just smiling.</description>
      <media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/exiagarden.github.io/posts/the-beauty-inside/feature.jpg" />
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Compassion In Humans And The Future</title>
      <link>exiagarden.github.io/posts/compassion-in-humans-and-the-future/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 23:32:30 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>exiagarden.github.io/posts/compassion-in-humans-and-the-future/</guid>
      <description>Do humans need to create a standard for compassion and empathy&gt; Do humans need to create a standard for compassion and empathy # We as humans are getting smarter with time but as all we do is get intelligence that doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean that are getting equally compassionate or moral. Going into the future with just intelligence is like shooting a gun but unable to see anything. It can lead to many disasters as people put their own self interests and wants before anything else.</description>
      <media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/exiagarden.github.io/posts/compassion-in-humans-and-the-future/feature.jpg" />
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Productivity Hacks</title>
      <link>exiagarden.github.io/posts/productivitty-hacks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Oct 2021 14:23:30 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>exiagarden.github.io/posts/productivitty-hacks/</guid>
      <description>1. Use A Calender&gt; 1. Use A Calender # Use calendar and time block to make sure you are doing what you&amp;rsquo;re supposed to be doing, this also helps with reminders.
2. Create A &amp;ldquo;Might-Do List&amp;rdquo; Of Daily Tasks&gt; 2. Create A &amp;ldquo;Might-Do List&amp;rdquo; Of Daily Tasks # These are the potential things I can do in the day.
Also add on &amp;ldquo;Highlight of the day&amp;rdquo; task. This is the most important task of the day, if this is done the day can be considered a success.</description>
      <media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/exiagarden.github.io/posts/productivitty-hacks/feature.jpg" />
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Compounded Relationships</title>
      <link>exiagarden.github.io/posts/compounded-relationships/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Aug 2021 13:41:30 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>exiagarden.github.io/posts/compounded-relationships/</guid>
      <description>Like compound interest in financial market and money we can also get compound interest/benefits in our relationships. Imagine investing in a good relationship for a long time, this relationship will give you more benefits than if you were to start that relationship and break it in between then start it again and do the same thing. With time relationships have the potential to grow at an exponential rate. It depends on how one manages the relationship.</description>
      <media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/exiagarden.github.io/posts/compounded-relationships/feature.jpg" />
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>