<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Permanent Notes on EXIA&#39;s Garden</title>
    <link>https://exiasgarden.pages.dev/categories/permanent-notes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Permanent Notes on EXIA&#39;s Garden</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2022 09:03:30 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://exiasgarden.pages.dev/categories/permanent-notes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>If You Don&#39;t Have Regrets You&#39;re Doing Life Wrong</title>
      <link>https://exiasgarden.pages.dev/posts/if-you-dont-have-regrets-youre-doing-life-wrong/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2022 09:03:30 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://exiasgarden.pages.dev/posts/if-you-dont-have-regrets-youre-doing-life-wrong/</guid>
      <description>We all are taught, &amp;ldquo;Live a life, where you don&amp;rsquo;t have any regrets&amp;rdquo;, You subscribe to the idea and think &amp;ldquo;OK, I&amp;rsquo;ll live a life, where I don&amp;rsquo;t have any regrets!&amp;rdquo;, This sounds great from a macro perspective, but once you start to look at things from a microscopic level you start to see how difficult and punishing this kind of mindset can be.
Just to be clear, I&amp;rsquo;m not going to be talking about the obvious things one must do to avoid regrets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>📱 Life Without Social Media</title>
      <link>https://exiasgarden.pages.dev/posts/life-without-social-media/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 15:28:30 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://exiasgarden.pages.dev/posts/life-without-social-media/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s a bit of an intro. The reason I uninstalled all my social media apps was with the realization that I might be too addicted to using these apps on a daily basis. The problem with any kind of addiction is that you don&amp;rsquo;t realize that you&amp;rsquo;re addicted. You&amp;rsquo;d see examples of these everywhere. Ask a chain smoker if they can stop smoking? And the answer will be something like, &amp;ldquo;I can stop whenever I want, it&amp;rsquo;s just that I don&amp;rsquo;t want to stop yet!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Is A PKM And Why Should You Care</title>
      <link>https://exiasgarden.pages.dev/posts/what-is-a-pkm/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 16:08:30 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://exiasgarden.pages.dev/posts/what-is-a-pkm/</guid>
      <description>PKM in its full form is known as personal knowledge management, is a system which helps you keep a database of all the knowledge that is important to you in your life. We all have the same problem, which is remembering things that help us make sense of the world.
You can use a PKM for anything that you&amp;rsquo;re into, like when you&amp;rsquo;re working on your PhD, or just want to remember what shows you watched or want to watch, or you stumbled upon a topic and don&amp;rsquo;t want to forget everything that you&amp;rsquo;ve learned by next week, or maybe you just want to track your habits, your workouts or your dreams and goals over time, or maybe you want to remember and cherish all the memories of your loved ones, or just and to remember how you&amp;rsquo;ve lived a good life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>🔎 Finding Meaning In Life With Friends And Family</title>
      <link>https://exiasgarden.pages.dev/posts/finding-meaning-with-friends-and-family/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 22:21:30 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://exiasgarden.pages.dev/posts/finding-meaning-with-friends-and-family/</guid>
      <description>Friends and family are the most important part of my life, like for many others. I cannot imagine my life without these people. Although it&amp;rsquo;s hard to explain what they mean to me or how friends and family can give your life meaning but, Here&amp;rsquo;s what I have. I might not be able to formulate all my thoughts properly, So I might add another post in the future.
They Love Me For Who I&amp;rsquo;m&gt; They Love Me For Who I&amp;rsquo;m # Friends and family love you for who you are.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>😇 How To Become A Good Friend</title>
      <link>https://exiasgarden.pages.dev/posts/how-to-be-a-good-friend/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2022 20:47:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://exiasgarden.pages.dev/posts/how-to-be-a-good-friend/</guid>
      <description>Who Is A Friend?&gt; Who Is A Friend? # It can be easy and hard to define what friendship is depending on who you&amp;rsquo;re talking to, but as I&amp;rsquo;m getting older the more I look into it, the better I feel about the friends that I have in my life.
So who is a friend? A friend can be anyone, even a family member, if they fulfil some of these roles -</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
