<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>🧊 Effects on EXIA&#39;s Garden</title>
    <link>https://exiasgarden.pages.dev/moc/effects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 🧊 Effects on EXIA&#39;s Garden</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 15:14:30 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://exiasgarden.pages.dev/moc/effects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Dunning Kruger Effect</title>
      <link>https://exiasgarden.pages.dev/moc/effects/dunning-kruger-effect/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 15:14:30 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://exiasgarden.pages.dev/moc/effects/dunning-kruger-effect/</guid>
      <description>What is the Dunning-Kruger Effect?&gt; What is the Dunning-Kruger Effect? # The Dunning-Kruger effect effect occurs when a person’s lack of knowledge and skills in a certain area cause them to overestimate their own competence. By contrast, this effect also causes those who excel in a given area to think the task is simple for everyone, and underestimate their relative abilities as well.
Where this bias occurs&gt; Where this bias occurs # Imagine you and your friends decide to try something new—separately, you all start learning Spanish.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ad Hominem</title>
      <link>https://exiasgarden.pages.dev/moc/effects/ad-hominem/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 08:41:30 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://exiasgarden.pages.dev/moc/effects/ad-hominem/</guid>
      <description>An ad hominem fallacy uses personal attacks rather than logic. This fallacy occurs when someone rejects or criticizes another point of view based on the personal characteristics, ethnic background, physical appearance, or other non-relevant traits of the person who holds it.
Ad Hominem arguments are often used in politics, where they are often called &amp;ldquo;mudslinging&amp;rdquo;.
People utilize ad hominem fallacy because they want to appeal to people&amp;rsquo;s emotions.
How to deal with ad hominem fallacy?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Pygmalion Effect</title>
      <link>https://exiasgarden.pages.dev/moc/effects/the-pygmalion-effect/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Aug 2021 02:45:30 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://exiasgarden.pages.dev/moc/effects/the-pygmalion-effect/</guid>
      <description>The pygmalion effect is a phenomena in which higher beliefs lead to higher performance. The pygmalion effect can be best understood by a circle. Our beliefs about other person influences our actions towards that person. Now this action has an impact on others beliefs about themselves. As others believes change it causes their actions to change. These actions again reinforce our believes about other person. which repeats the cycle. Imagine if I tell a girl that she is beautiful because I believe so, this will affect her belief and will help her take her beauty more seriously.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
