<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Level 64 on EXIA&#39;s Garden</title>
    <link>https://exiasgarden.pages.dev/moc/level-64/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Level 64 on EXIA&#39;s Garden</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2022 06:59:30 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://exiasgarden.pages.dev/moc/level-64/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>What Alcohol Does To Your Body, Brain &amp; Health</title>
      <link>https://exiasgarden.pages.dev/moc/level-64/what-alcohol-does-to-your-body-brain-health/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2022 06:59:30 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://exiasgarden.pages.dev/moc/level-64/what-alcohol-does-to-your-body-brain-health/</guid>
      <description>All of the text is converted from a diagram that I made as it&amp;rsquo;s quite hard to showcase the whole diagram here&gt; All of the text is converted from a diagram that I made as it&amp;rsquo;s quite hard to showcase the whole diagram here # Even low consumption of alcohol, such as 1 drink per day (or 5-7 a week) has been shown to cause thinning of neocortex and other brain regions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>✍🏻 Learn To Write</title>
      <link>https://exiasgarden.pages.dev/moc/level-64/learn-to-write/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Nov 2022 14:45:30 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://exiasgarden.pages.dev/moc/level-64/learn-to-write/</guid>
      <description>Jordan Peterson says that in order to think well its best to learn to write. When you can organize your thoughts well on a paper (or in this any digital format like this one) it helps you see things better in your head. And he is not the first one to say this I think.
I remember writing something similar when I was writing a post on insightfulsage.com. It said something similar, that organzing your thoughts on a paper helps you see them clearly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Not Watching Porn Changes Your Mind</title>
      <link>https://exiasgarden.pages.dev/moc/level-64/how-not-watching-porn-changes-your-mind/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 00:28:30 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://exiasgarden.pages.dev/moc/level-64/how-not-watching-porn-changes-your-mind/</guid>
      <description>The effects of watching porn is already discussed in one of my previous notes Thoughts On Masturbation And Porn. So in this one we&amp;rsquo;ll just focus on what changes when we don&amp;rsquo;t watch porn.
It Has No Net Positive&gt; It Has No Net Positive # Porn overall has no real purpose in your life. We have gotten used to porn in recent years just because we now have the access to it, with fast internet and way too much porn content that&amp;rsquo;s produced on a daily basis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Theories About God &amp; Universe</title>
      <link>https://exiasgarden.pages.dev/moc/level-64/theories-about-god-universe/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 22:24:30 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://exiasgarden.pages.dev/moc/level-64/theories-about-god-universe/</guid>
      <description>I have a few things that I want to put down here as my theories as to how God has designed the universe to function. These theories have evolved over time and will continue to change as I think more about these things and get more knowledge over time.
We Go Through A Cycle Of Re-Birth&gt; We Go Through A Cycle Of Re-Birth # We go through a cycle of rebirth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Core Idea Time Management</title>
      <link>https://exiasgarden.pages.dev/moc/level-64/core-idea-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 12:21:30 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://exiasgarden.pages.dev/moc/level-64/core-idea-management/</guid>
      <description>Capture&gt; Capture # Find a system that works for YOU. A system where you can capture all your ideas, tasks, projects, and relevant information. Preferably a system that allows you to overview and review all that information on a regular basis.
Configure&gt; Configure # &amp;ldquo;Care more about how you actually organize this information that you are capturing&amp;rdquo;. Structure the information that you have captured, whether it is by categories or by role, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>❤️‍🔥 The Beauty Inside</title>
      <link>https://exiasgarden.pages.dev/moc/level-64/the-beauty-inside/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 04:15:30 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://exiasgarden.pages.dev/moc/level-64/the-beauty-inside/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s a beauty inside all of us, although we may not see it all the time but, there are times when we see a glimpse of this beauty.
It can be a strangers smile, It can be a gesture, it can be anything that gives us a window to see into the souls of others.
Yesterday I saw a blind girl walking down the street, I don&amp;rsquo;t know what she was thinking but was just smiling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Communicating Better</title>
      <link>https://exiasgarden.pages.dev/moc/level-64/communicating-better/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Dec 2021 01:06:30 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://exiasgarden.pages.dev/moc/level-64/communicating-better/</guid>
      <description>Master the ability to listen and understand.
As a man who is evolved to fix &amp;amp; solve problems. It becomes a habit to listen to someone’s problems and try to find quick solutions but this is not always the right thing to do. Sometimes people especially, women who are evolved to share their problems and communicate things with each other, Always trying to find a solution or fixing the issues is not the agenda.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Compassion In Humans And The Future</title>
      <link>https://exiasgarden.pages.dev/moc/level-64/compassion-in-humans-and-the-future/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 23:32:30 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://exiasgarden.pages.dev/moc/level-64/compassion-in-humans-and-the-future/</guid>
      <description>Do humans need to create a standard for compassion and empathy&gt; Do humans need to create a standard for compassion and empathy # We as humans are getting smarter with time but as all we do is get intelligence that doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean that are getting equally compassionate or moral. Going into the future with just intelligence is like shooting a gun but unable to see anything. It can lead to many disasters as people put their own self interests and wants before anything else.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts On Masturbation And Porn</title>
      <link>https://exiasgarden.pages.dev/moc/level-64/thoughts-on-masturbation-and-porn/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 12:41:30 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://exiasgarden.pages.dev/moc/level-64/thoughts-on-masturbation-and-porn/</guid>
      <description>How watching porn can rewire our brain&gt; How watching porn can rewire our brain # Having the option to see many women in that position where your primal mind sees them as a sexual partner is something we didn&amp;rsquo;t have a few decades also. The option to fast-forward, click to another tab and have endless option of items to see and get excited from create a huge problem when it comes to how we see sex as a whole.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Productivity Hacks</title>
      <link>https://exiasgarden.pages.dev/moc/level-64/productivitty-hacks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Oct 2021 14:23:30 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://exiasgarden.pages.dev/moc/level-64/productivitty-hacks/</guid>
      <description>1. Use A Calender&gt; 1. Use A Calender # Use calendar and time block to make sure you are doing what you&amp;rsquo;re supposed to be doing, this also helps with reminders.
2. Create A &amp;ldquo;Might-Do List&amp;rdquo; Of Daily Tasks&gt; 2. Create A &amp;ldquo;Might-Do List&amp;rdquo; Of Daily Tasks # These are the potential things I can do in the day.
Also add on &amp;ldquo;Highlight of the day&amp;rdquo; task. This is the most important task of the day, if this is done the day can be considered a success.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MILES framework</title>
      <link>https://exiasgarden.pages.dev/moc/level-64/miles-framework/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Oct 2021 01:02:30 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://exiasgarden.pages.dev/moc/level-64/miles-framework/</guid>
      <description> A framework from the book &amp;lsquo;Unfair Advantage.&amp;rsquo; MILES framework talks about how one can get an unfair advantage with things like Money, Intelligence, Insight, Luck, Education, Expertise, and Status. You can have any one of multiple of these advantages. It&amp;rsquo;s a matter of recognizing what you have and playing to your strengths. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unfair Advantage</title>
      <link>https://exiasgarden.pages.dev/moc/level-64/unfair-advantage/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Oct 2021 00:37:30 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://exiasgarden.pages.dev/moc/level-64/unfair-advantage/</guid>
      <description>An unfair advantage is something that cannot be easily copied or bought by your competitor. Success is a combination fair play and unfair advantages. Success = Fair Play + Unfair Advantages. Fair play = Getting up early, hustling, Working hard on your business. Unfair Advantage = Getting 500k from your parents to start up your own business. Types of unfair advantages one can have or the [[MILES framework]]. = Money, Intelligence, Insight, Location, Luck, Education, Expertise, Status.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Selective Understanding Flaws Of Humans</title>
      <link>https://exiasgarden.pages.dev/moc/level-64/selective-understanding-flaws-of-humans/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Sep 2021 00:26:30 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://exiasgarden.pages.dev/moc/level-64/selective-understanding-flaws-of-humans/</guid>
      <description>Often times we consider ourselves as an understanding person. Although how true this can be depends on person-to-person. There are times that even an understanding person might not be able to understand somethings. A person can be very oblivious to some aspects even though they might be very well in others. This can affect relationships if not taken care of properly. We often make the perception that if a person didn&amp;rsquo;t understand it the first time, they might not understand it ever again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Compounded Relationships</title>
      <link>https://exiasgarden.pages.dev/moc/level-64/compounded-relationships/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Aug 2021 13:41:30 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://exiasgarden.pages.dev/moc/level-64/compounded-relationships/</guid>
      <description>Like compound interest in financial market and money we can also get compound interest/benefits in our relationships. Imagine investing in a good relationship for a long time, this relationship will give you more benefits than if you were to start that relationship and break it in between then start it again and do the same thing. With time relationships have the potential to grow at an exponential rate. It depends on how one manages the relationship.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
